http://www.bvu.edu/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Site Search
Skip to main site navigation
Skip to main content
FacebookTwitterYoutubeInstagramInformation for...StudentsFaculty/StaffFamiliesDirectoryA-Z Index
Privacy PolicyUpdated Nov. 8, 2017Buena Vista University is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected when using our website. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this policy.We may change this policy occasionally by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are fully informed of our policy.Personal InformationBuena Vista University may collect personal information for the purpose of maintaining relationships with prospective students, alumni, and other external audiences. Any personal information submitted on our website is for the specified use of Buena Vista University and will only be used by Buena Vista University. We will not sell or share this information with any third party for any purpose outside of official University business, except for certain circumstances in which disclosure is required by law.Information we collect may include, but is not limited to, the following:Name and contact information, including email addressDemographic information such as preferences and academic interestsOther information relevant to your relationship with Buena Vista UniversityWe may require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better service. Buena Vista University may use your information in the following ways:Send email or printed materials promoting university programs, features and facilities.Facilitate inquiry and enrollment as a Buena Vista University student.Share your personal and professional achievements with interested audiences.Customize the website according to your interests.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. However, there may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. We therefore disclaim any warranties or representations relating to nondisclosure of private information.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Analytics and measurementWhen you visit the Buena Vista University website, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, pages visited, and average time spent on pages. This information is used to improve web design, information architecture, and user experience.Contact informationYou may contact us if:You have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy.Wish to make corrections to any personal information you have provided.Want to opt out of receiving future promotional correspondence, including emails, from Buena Vista University.Contact information may be found on our “Contact Us” page.
